No ! No !
Help ... help !
Are you still going into town , doctor ?
You see that 's how one gets greeted in the village .
Death rules here .
If I may , please give me 50 crowns . I am sorry , but I cannot go on from here .
Sorry , I gave you a ride to this place , because I needed the money .
The inn is further ahead , after that arch .
It won 't be difficult for you to find it .
Just ask for directions , it 's the only inn in town .
You see this is a condemned place , a God forgotten place .
Nobody ever comes to this place .
You better come back , doctor , before it is too late .
I am looking for the inn . Can you tell me where it is ?
It 's over there .
I 'm looking for the inspector .
Inspector Kruger .
You are the doctor , aren 't you ?
In this village , we never liked doctors .
Quiet !
Dr. Eswai ?
Yes !
Come . Come . The inspector is waiting for you .
Enough !
I said I know nothing about Irene Hollander .
I didn 't know her , inspector !
You , too , know nothing , haven 't seen or heard anything ?
You all have the same answer ! Look , you can 't fool me !
Why such reluctance ? What keeps your tongue tied ?
Is it fear maybe ? Fear from what ? Tell me ! From what ?
An amulet !
That 's what 's keeping you from talking . It 's superstition , ignorance .
But , I will get you to talk !
So that you will tell me what happened , you 'll see !
You made it . I was getting worried about you .
I left immediately , but it wasn 't easy getting here , Inspector Kruger .
We are isolated from the world here , nobody ever comes to see us .
This is Mr. Keirr , the burgomeister .
Go , but wait with the others downstairs .
Have you lived here for a while , Inspector ?
I arrived here the other day .
I asked for you to come here for a very serious matter .
Take a look at this letter .
It 's from Irena Hollander , a girl who worked as a housekeeper at a villa .
The villa of the Baroness Graps .
I can 't resist it anymore .
I have decided to talk , to break the cycle of death ...
a great burden to me .
Come soon , because this time it feels like it 's my turn . Irena Hollander .
That letter came to the police station ...
and I came here to check what was indeed true .
The girl , unfortunately , was already dead .
Impaled by the spears of a gate .
A homicide !
I still don 't know .
They keep wanting me to believe that it is a curse .
But this letter makes me think about something totally different .
But it will be up to you to figure it out , doctor .
You 'll have to do an autopsy .
Burgomeister , we 'll continue with the interview tomorrow .
Nobody can leave !
Have you figured something out , Inspector ?
I keep hitting a wall of silence .
They are afraid , of everything .
They are afraid of my questions , it 's as if they are being terrorized by something .
On the other hand , I understand their distrust towards strangers .
You are without doubt the first authority who has made it to this place .
Their only belief system is superstition .
Earlier , they were carrying a casket ...
A casket ? When ?
When I arrived .
I think I get it now .
They are trying to prevent an autopsy on Irena Hollander !
Come with me , doctor , quickly !
Rufus , Argo ! Stop !
What are you doing ?
Who told you to bury her ? Wasn 't I clear enough ?
The doctor came for the very purpose of doing an autopsy !
It 's against the law of nature to touch the dead .
Take her to the mortuary .
When can you start ?
Right away . But a qualified witness is needed .
There are guidelines I have to follow .
I told you to move the corpse inside , immediately !
As to the witness , don 't worry . I 'll send you ...
Inspector ! Inspector ! The burgomeister sent me !
He wants you to come back to the inn .
He couldn 't keep the people you were trying to interview .
He wants to talk to you immediately !
Okay , I am coming .
Go do what you have to do . Once you 're done , come join me .
All right .
Mr. Keirr !
Why have they all left ?
I am sorry ! But there was nothing I could do about it .
I tried to keep them here for the interrogation .
But once they found out that you had gone to the cemetery , they ran away .
Evidently you don 't have much power over these people .
Well , it 's not a matter of power .
Inspector , I beg you ! Stop the autopsy !
I have to solve this case !
Listen to me ! You must not let the body of Irena Hollander be touched .
I was hoping that you would cooperate with me .
I see that you are siding with them , to hide the truth .
No ! No , Inspector !
I made you come back , to explain to you ...
the village does not speak , not to cover up something ...
but out of fear .
I am not ashamed to admit that I am afraid ...
about what may happen to me ...
if I reveal ...
the secret of Villa Graps .
Villa Graps ?
It sounds like an impossible story , something above the laws of nature .
It will be difficult for you to believe me .
But the death of Irena Hollander ...
is not due to an accident .
It is murder !
Are you Dr. Eswai ?
I am Monica Schuftan . The Inspector sent me to assist you .
I was actually looking for a physician .
I am a science student from Grottenburg .
I am the only one here who will be useful to you .
So , you are from the village ?
Yes , I was born there . But I have gone since I was one year old .
I returned on the same day this girl died .
Have you ever attended an autopsy ?
No , never .
That 's incredible !
They slipped a coin into her heart !
Just like the legend says .
It 's an old legend , which has been circulating around here for centuries .
It says that only a coin in the heart would bring peace ...
to those whose lives ended violently .
In spite of the autopsy , we are unable to conclude ...
whether we are talking about an accident or a suicide .
Oh , that coin !
Who could have slipped it into the heart of that poor girl ?
And why ?
Don 't worry about it , Monica .
Inspector Kruger will clear up everything .
I am here now , this is where I live .
I am Mrs. Morano 's guest .
I don 't mean to be intrusive , but why did you come back to this village ?
I came back to visit my parents ' graves . I never knew them .
They left me with a small fund , which I lived off before going to college .
Thank you for telling me . You have been really brave .
Thanks . I wish you a good night , doctor .
Good night , Monica .
I already told you , doctor , not to touch the dead .
He who touches them has to pay with his life .
We had to , we had to bury that girl !
Why didn 't you do that ?
Stop it !
Doctor !
Doctor , the inspector went to Villa Graps because of an emergency .
He left an hour ago and left you a note in his room .
Didn 't he say when he would be back ?
Nobody ever makes it back from Villa Graps .
Why are you saying this ?
I didn 't say that . I didn 't say that .
It 's not true . Stay away .
Go to your room right away . Dinner is ready .
No !
No ! No ! Not me ! I didn 't say anything , I didn 't say a thing !
Darling , what 's happening to you ?
At the window !
Did you see her ?
Oh my God , that 's terrible !
Now that she is scared , there 's no more hope !
Only Ruth can do something .
Go and get her ! Quickly , hurry !
You were looking for me , right ?
I could feel that you needed me .
Dear Eswai ...
the burgomeister revealed things to me that I find unbelievable .
I am heading to Villa Graps to meet the Baroness ...
to inquire about something important .
Join me there as soon as you can . Sincerely , Inspector Kruger .
Calm down , girl . It won 't happen to you .
The curse will not touch you .
Get her undressed .
Blood ! Strengthen yourself . Death will not touch you .
Stay away , stay far away from the Villa .
Stay far away !
Stay away !
I heard her .
She 's here ! It 's because I opened my mouth !
Don 't say that , darling daughter !
I tell you , I heard her !
This will protect you .
You can never take it off .
I am done now .
No , no , go out this way . They cannot see you .
I helped her pay her bill .
Why did you exorcise this girl ?
You can help me here .
You certainly must know a lot about this village .
Why do people seek help in your magical skills ?
What are they afraid of ?
There is a terrible curse hovering over these people .
Be careful , you , too , are in danger .
Irena Hollander was thrown to her death .
But , by what ?
Leave , doctor ! Those are things that science cannot explain .
Give the inspector a warning right away . Send him away as well .
And stop this investigation .
Inspector Kruger is at Villa Graps to wrap up the interrogation .
He is a practical and driven man . He doesn 't get influenced by imagination .
He will get to the bottom of the matter .
Where is the Villa ? I 'd like to join the inspector .
Don 't go , doctor . Don 't go there . I mean it .
They talk about this villa with such terror ...
as if even afraid to say its name . It 's something I need to clarify .
Villa Graps is over there .
Wait a moment .
You can 't tell me anything about this coin either ?
I found it today inside Irena Hollander 's heart .
I was hoping that you would help me understand .
I already told you that I know nothing . Go ahead , if you wish .
But still not too late for you to choose not to go .
Thank you . I hope we will meet again .
If he ever makes it back from that villa .
Keirr , my love .
What 's the matter , Keirr ?
And there is another one .
It is a mortal chain this one , and it will never break !
Death rules at Villa Graps .
Yes , there is death .
It can be stopped only by death itself .
Leave now , Keirr . We have to call the hearse right away .
You know the dirt has to cover the body immediately before the sun rises .
With its weight , the dirt embraces the dead ...
and keeps it in the earth forever .
They won 't take you with them .
You will be at peace .
Kruger !
Inspector Kruger !
What do you want ?
Excuse me , I am looking for Mr. Kruger , the inspector .
There is no inspector .
But I was told that he came to see Baroness Graps .
I am the Baroness Graps .
And nobody ever comes here . I am alone here in this villa . Leave !
No , wait !
Leave ! It 's for your own good !
Leave me alone !
Hi .
What 's your name ?
Melissa !
My name is Melissa .
Melissa ?
Melissa !
Oh no , no ! No , no , no !
Mrs. Morano , I beg you ! Mrs. Morano !
What do you want ?
Open up ! Mrs. Morano , I am afraid ! Open up , I beg you !
Go away ! What goes around comes around .
You shouldn 't have touched that girl !
Paul !
Monica ! What are you doing here ?
I came to see you .
What 's wrong ?
I had a nightmare . I got scared .
I couldn 't stand it anymore !
Calm down . You must be shaken by the autopsy .
The cord isn 't moving .
Take me away , Paul . Take me away from here .
Did you see that ? It was the wind .
No , no , it wasn 't the wind .
It 's the hatred , the bell is being moved by the hatred .
It always sounds this way when someone has to die .
It 's been this way since she died without a drop of blood in her .
Who ?
It was a seven-year-old girl .
She would hang on to those cords of the bell , looking for help !
Her name was Melissa .
Melissa .
Listen , the lady will stay here this night . Let them prepare a room for her .
And , has Inspector Kruger come back yet ?
No , I haven 't seen him .
Martha !
Yes ?
Martha , go upstairs . We need to get a room ready for the lady .
Right away .
Paul ! Did you hear what the innkeeper said ?
It wasn 't the wind making the bell sound !
Monica ! Don 't let it affect you this way !
But this is not like in the other cases .
Even the church is condemned .
It 's a wreck . People seem to have no faith anymore .
No , they are just people in poor spirits , victims of superstition .
Miss , you can come upstairs now .
Good night , Monica .
Good night , Paul . And thank you .
Nadienne !
Nadienne , what 's wrong ?
You are boiling , such high fever ! What are you feeling ?
What are you doing here ? What do you want ?
Leave ! This is none of your business !
Isn 't she suffering enough already ?
You can 't touch her ! Let it be !
A cilice !
What have you done ? Are you crazy ? Do you want her to die ?
Madmen ! Your methods are absurd .
She could die of these wounds .
My daughter will die anyway . Nothing can save her .
Shut up ! Quiet !
Don 't worry , Nadienne .
It will all be over , you 'll see .
It 's nothing bad .
They ... they picked me .
They picked me ! They picked me !
I know I won 't be saved . I know .
She is very agitated . Her pulse is irregular .
What should we do ?
She needs to rest . I will give her a sedative .
I left my luggage in the inspector 's room . Let 's go , Martha .
Give this to her when she wakes up , not more than 20 drops !
- Don 't hesitate if you need me . - Thank you , doctor .
Furthermore I feel it necessary not to say anything about ...
what the burgomeister Karl told me , Inspector Kruger , after several meetings .
The burgomeister says that the village suffers from a nightmare of a curse ...
that started with the death of little Melissa Graps .
Since then , according to the belief of these people ...
Melissa keeps returning by appearing to the living .
To make matters even more incredible ...
the people Melissa appears to , each die under mysterious circumstances ...
which the farmers call supernatural .
Let 's hurry ! There 's no time to waste .
Hurry , hurry !
Paul .
There are lights at the cemetery . What might that be ?
Yes , I saw them , too .
It could be Inspector Kruger . Maybe he has discovered something .
No , don 't go there !
I 'm not sure if it 's Inspector Kruger down there .
What would he be doing down there at night ?
I don 't know .
But I want to see what 's going on .
Kruger ... !
No , no !
The burgomeister lives here .
Keirr !
Mr. Keirr !
Yes , I am here . Come on in .
Come in , doctor .
I knew you would come .
I found the body of Inspector Kruger at the cemetery .
I know . I arranged for it to be taken there .
He died by a gunshot to his temple .
Don 't use this tone with me . I didn 't say that I killed him .
Another victim of the demonic forces , right ?
And maybe even he had a coin in his heart !
Yes .
To keep his spirit from answering to the call ...
of Melissa .
I understand this may seem impossible to a man of science like you .
I read what you reported to Inspector Kruger .
You can 't expect me to believe those legends !
I didn 't believe them , either .
They aren 't legends ...
but a horrible reality instead .
In the last few years more than ten people were thrown to their deaths .
All of them were sane , without worries .
None of them had enemies .
We are all in danger here .
Listen to me , Eswai .
Leave as soon as possible .
You , too , Miss , leave !
You should have never come to this village !
I was born here and the bodies of my parents are resting here .
The tombs you placed your flowers on ...
are not the graves of your parents .
The Schuftans never had any children .
No ...
That 's impossible . That 's not true .
This is another absurd invention .
I have proof as to what I have said .
The Schuftans left me a sealed envelope ...
to give to you in case you should return .
I kept it in my utmost care .
The Schuftans were servants at the Villa Graps .
Your fate , like ours , is connected to this Villa .
I will bring you that envelope now .
Remember , doctor ...
the answer you are looking for can be found at the Villa Graps .
Do you think there is some truth to it ?
Keirr !
No ... No ...
Open up ! Open !
Monica !
I can 't take this anymore !
I can 't take this !
Stop it for God 's sake !
They will kill all of us here !
Stop it !
Help .
Let 's go get someone .
Come .
Come out !
The burgomeister is dead ! Cowards !
You are such cowards , you 'll get yourselves all killed !
Nobody will ever help us . They are afraid !
Let 's go .
Go away , you murderer !
You killed my daughter Nadienne , enough now !
Leave , leave !
Damn you ! It 's your fault that my daughter is dead !
Go away ! Leave or I kill you !
Let 's go .
Monica !
Where are you ?
Monica , what 's the matter ?
How strange , Paul .
I came here as if I already knew this passage .
It feels like I have already been here .
Paul , I 've never been here ...
yet I feel like I have already seen this place before .
We are locked inside , the lock has snapped shut .
There is nothing I can do . It 's impossible to open it .
Let 's find another exit .
This must be the Graps family crypt .
Melissa Graps .
Maybe we can get out from there .
No , it 's not possible . It 's locked down there .
Paul !
It 's Melissa .
Melissa ... Melissa .
My little girl . My daughter .
Why did you come here ?
You shouldn 't break the peace of my little one .
Why ?
Baroness , terrible things are happening in the village !
The village gets what it deserves !
They always hated us , the Graps family !
They let my little girl die twenty years ago .
The village was celebrating , everybody was drunk .
One of them ran her over with a horse .
She begged for help for a long time , desperately ...
but nobody would help her .
In my opinion , they should all be condemned !
And she bled to death .
Bastards !
Come , come !
Please , come .
Come .
I left her room as it was .
Here ... she would play here .
She was full of life . Happy , always without worries .
She liked to see herself in the mirror .
She wasn 't able to reach up there . She had to stand on her toes here .
This was her favorite doll .
Everything has stayed the same as she had left it .
With her dolls ... she had so many of them ...
Melissa !
Paul !
No !
You have recovered , Dr. Eswai .
You are lucky . I found you in the park just in the nick of time .
You , too , were plunging towards death .
The silver coin .
At this point I can 't do anything else for my dear Keirr ...
The silver in your heart will bring you eternal peace .
I did everything I could to keep him from dying .
I have dreaded this moment day by day .
I loved you so much !
My life without you has no more purpose .
I will vindicate you , Keirr .
I will go to Villa Graps , even if it will cost me my life .
And Monica ... Where is Monica ?
There is no more hope for Monica .
She is Melissa 's sister , the second daughter of the Baroness Graps .
Yes , Monica , you are my little girl .
I knew that you would come back to me . Wait .
The Schuftans were my servants .
I was the one who kept you in college .
If you really are my mother , why would you do such a thing ?
Well , in order to keep you away from the Villa .
I was worried for your life .
This is you , Monica .
You were two years old .
And there is Melissa , your sister .
After Melissa 's deadly accident ...
they all died in this Villa by Melissa 's hatred .
Melissa cannot hate anymore now , she is all ashes by now .
No !
No . You saw her . She is still here .
She uses me to return among the living .
I am a medium with supernatural powers ...
which I cannot control .
See , with these irresistible powers , I am their victim .
They draw their strength from me , in order to survive .
I know ... I know that they are evil .
But I can 't stop them , I am their slave , they constantly force me ...
to call upon them !
No ! No ! No ! All of this is absurd , unreal !
I have to find Paul . Please , help me .
Take care of yourself ! Leave !
Here , they are coming . I feel them .
Let them go !
No . I can 't let go of them .
Go away ! I said leave !
You should go as well . Melissa has been waiting for you for twenty years .
Leave !
Melissa !
Melissa ... Melissa ...
Enough !
Baroness Graps , you are done killing .
I have finally decided to put an end to this curse .
Ruth ...
you are playing with your fate .
Because it says you will die in this house .
This doesn 't matter to me anymore .
I will put an end to this curse .
No , you have no powers over them .
You will die , too .
I have to vindicate Keirr . You shouldn 't have killed him .
Your time has come !
You will pay for what you did to him and all the other innocent victims !
You are the cause of all that 's happened .
You who calls upon past spirits to use for your hatred ...
that has driven you since your daughter died !
No ! It 's them , it 's not my fault .
It 's them who force me to do so . It 's not my fault .
It is them who force me to do those things . No !
You call upon Melissa with your skills as a medium ...
in order to invade and throw to their death the people of this village .
They could not use their free will ...
and those poor people were unable to resist .
But now your maleficent powers are coming to an end !
" To an end ... " ?
You are a murderer !
You even want to kill your own daughter Monica .
Yes , I hate her as well .
The Schuftans kidnapped her from me and escaped through a tunnel .
They didn 't want Melissa to get to them .
I hate them all . You will die .
You will all obey me , all of you !
Monica !
Monica ! Open for God 's sake !
Die you damned bitch !
You and all your demonic creatures !
Monica !
This nightmare has now come to an end !
The chain of death has finally been broken .